Juan Jose Vasquez Sesteaga

Profile

IT support with focus on customer service, 3 years experience on Technical Support. Troubleshooting hardware, remote and phone disposal with emergency problems. Software and OS set up, analytics on customer IT demands and needs, Preventive and corrective maintenance schedule.

Experience

Refacciones Los Mochis: IT Support

Jun 2021 - Now

- POS Setup:third party software POS installation and hardware set up(printers, scanner, thermal printer and PC).
- Network Setup: Cable management and distribution around the shop for wifi extension, cameras and PC's.
- Corrective and preventive maintenance: Schedule for cleaning hardware and clear cache and unused software in OS.

Carso: ISP Installation Technician

May 2020 - May 2021

- Telmex Network: Provide the DSL connection between Telmex centrals and customers modem.
- Customer Support: Communication from start to finish on internet installation with some advice on modem placement and information about frequency bands(5G and 2.4G) with 2 months of warranty support.
- Inventory Management: Responsable of installation material and tools such as a car, cable tester and tone and tool box.

S&B Entretenimientos(Casino Palace): Technical Support

May 2018 - Feb 2020

- Hardware troubleshooting: Casino machines(Customs PC's) repair, replace faulty parts as well as buttons and peripherals(monitors, touchscreen)
- CCTV design project: Make a CCTV layout covering camera positions and cable management as well as DVR setup with supervision and presentation to the Casino Manager.
- Customer Support: Answer to in operation calls to bring tech support to customers

Education

Universidad Tecnológica de Nogales: Técnico en Tecnologías de la Información

Contact Info

Juan Jose Vasquez Sesteaga

juanv91.cv@gmail.com

+52 631 124 61 50

Address

Ébano 24D Jardines del bosque Nogales Sonora Mexico

Skills

Help Desk

Technical Support

Problem Solving

User Training

Maintenance

Customer Service

Empathy

User Experience

Patience

Networking

Cable Management

Modem Configuration

IP configuration